Shrujan Shetty

A passionate Front-End engineer with over 10 years of experience in Vanilla Javascript, typescript, and JS frameworks like Angular and React. Proficient in object-oriented design development with good problem-solving skills.

Panaji Goa. India 7204347725 shrork@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

Persistent Systems

April 2018 - PRESENT

- Coordinated with multiple remote teams spread across different countries to design and develop a product for our client in Angular 11 and React.
- Worked on an application that scans user's cloud accounts, and identifies problems with them as per GDPR and HIPAA standards.
- Delivered new complex features promptly while maintaining high coding standards.
- Lead and mentored the team of freshers to impart knowledge and get the task done on time.
- Coordinated with UX team and developed Ul templates using web technologies like flexbox, and grids to develop a dashboard for our application.
- Optimized existing code base to improve the performance and usability of the application.
- Interacted with the client to give product demos and got inputs to further improve the user experience.
- Attended daily standup meetings with the client to show progress and highlight potential issues.
- Committed the code to GitLab, GitHub daily

Techjini Solutions (DataMatics)

July 2012 - March 2018

- Began my career by working in a startup company where I implemented multiple projects using Vanilla JavaScript and JavaScript-based frameworks like Angular JS.
- Developed a responsive web application using web technologies like HTML, CSS, and PHP to keep track of employees and the leaves taken by them.
- Collaborated with a large team to design a portal where the customers can view their advertisment, and manage, track, optimize and measure campaigns across brands.
- Implemented the Front-end Web Design of the portal using Vanilla JavaScript, HTML, and CSS promoting a brand through a movie for kids.

SKILLS

JavaScript ES6, HTML 5, CSS, SCSS, Angular, React, JSON, and Rest API

AWARDS

Received multiple client appreciations. (2021-22)

Superior Customer Service Award (2017)

Beyond the call of duty (2014)

LANGUAGES

English, Hindi, Konkani, and Tulu

SOME PROJECTS

ClearData — Cloud catalyst. Healthcare protector

ClearData offers one of the best solutions to the healthcare industry to protect their patient's information. By adopting modern cloud technologies, healthcare organizations can be sure that sensitive data is private, secure, and compliant.

Visto — Digital Advertising Platform

A digital advertising platform used by Agencies and Media Companies. It provides a platform-agnostic ad hub with a single interface to manage, track, optimize and measure campaigns across brands, products, regions, and agencies and also provides reports.

Bumble Bee Seafoods — Hero Of Color City

This project was developed to promote the film named HOCC (Hero Of Color City). This is a web application through which kids can play a few games and adults can learn to prepare tasty recipes.

Boston Marathon World Run — Virtual Marathon

A virtual marathon to raise money for the victims of the 2014 Boston bombing. Here the participants can click and upload pictures of themselves and upload them to the site. Users can also view the pictures in the gallery.

EDUCATION

AIMIT, Mangalore— MCA

2009 - 2012

Don Bosco College, Panaji — BCA

2006 - 2009